# **Nguyen Vinh Thien**

## **Fresher Developer**

**Phone:** 0394 756 393

Email: vinhthien1996@gmail.com

Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/vinhthien1996">https://www.facebook.com/vinhthien1996</a>

**Github:** <a href="https://github.com/vinhthien1996">https://github.com/vinhthien1996</a> **CV:** <a href="http://vinhthien-cv.herokuapp.com">http://vinhthien-cv.herokuapp.com</a>

### **ABOUT ME**

I'm Nguyen Vinh Thien - I work as a designer with 2-year experience. Since April 2020, I decided to left my job to comeback with the major that I have learnt at the university - Web Develop. I try to learn some up-to-date technologies, create unique and awesome functions for website and more. My target is trying to be a professional developer and working in creative and motivating environment.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

### **TopDev**

10/2020 - 12/2020

Position: Intern Developer (Laravel)

Responsibilities:

- Research available source code.
- Develop some more simple functions from the existing project.

04/2019 - 05/2020

Nguyen Gia Media

Posotion: Designer Responsibilities:

 Website administration, banner design, standee, advertising video editing for brand advertising.

#### **EDUCATION**

09/2020 - Present

**CyberSoft Academy** 

Front-end (ReactJS, Angular), Fulstack (NodeJS, VueJS)

07/2020 - 10/2020

**Korea IT School** 

Java web (Spring MVC)

08/2015 - 08/2018

Vinh Long University of Technology Education

Software Application

GPA: 3.59/4

# ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, ReactJS, Redux, NodeJS, Java, PHP
- (Laravel), MySQL, MongoDB, GIT
- English (Basic Reading Comprehension)

### **PROJECT**

In my free time, I work on some projects:

- Git: <a href="https://github.com/vinhthien1996">https://github.com/vinhthien1996</a>
- Weather App

http://vinhthien-weather-app.herokuapp.com/

- Clone Tix Homepage

http://vinhthien-tix.surge.sh/

- Clone Udemy Old Homepage

http://vinhthien-udemy.surge.sh/

- Movie Star Homepage

http://vinhthien-bootstrap.surge.sh/